<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IsaEs</title>
    <link>https://isaes.com.tr/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IsaEs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 11:39:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://isaes.com.tr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WSL ile Linux geliştirme ortamı hazırlama</title>
      <link>https://isaes.com.tr/posts/2020-09-05-setting-up-wsl-enviroment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 11:39:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaes.com.tr/posts/2020-09-05-setting-up-wsl-enviroment/</guid>
      <description>WSL yani Windows Subsystem for Linux&amp;rsquo;in ilk sürümü yaklaşık 4 sene önce son kararlı ikinci sürümü wsl2 ise bir sene önce piyasaya sürüldü. Ben ise wsl&amp;rsquo;i yaklaşık 3 aydır kullanıyorum ilk deneyimlerim ise gayet sorunsuzdu. Şuan kişisel projelerimde geliştirme ortamı olarak tamamen WSL kullanıyorum. Öncesinde geliştirme ortamı olarak kullandığım dual-boot linuxuma girmeme nerdeyse hiç gerek kalmadı diyebilirim. Windows WSL ile beni kendine kazandı. Bu yazımda ise Visual Studio Code ve WSL ve Windows terminal uygulamaları kullanarak kendimize işlevsel ve hoş görünümlü bir geliştirme ortamı hazırlayacağımızı anlatmaya çalışacağım.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File operation examples in NodeJs</title>
      <link>https://isaes.com.tr/posts/2020-08-14-file-operation-examples-in-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 18:43:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaes.com.tr/posts/2020-08-14-file-operation-examples-in-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>Reading and writing files is from the first requirement of programming. When it comes to a point you will probably have to code. When I started to computer engineering our first-week assignments include reading and writing from file and includes some calculations. From then in my jobs and project, i often need reading and writing from the filesystem.
I genuinely love to use javascript. It&amp;rsquo;s my first personal choice for when I need to create some scripting solution for my tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Commands Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://isaes.com.tr/posts/2019-03-09-some-useful-git-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 21:59:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaes.com.tr/posts/2019-03-09-some-useful-git-commands/</guid>
      <description>I sometimes struggle remembering simple commands and need to look some cheats sheet.These are the ones I have kept from the moment when started to using git. I started to learn git little bit late then others but after started to using git. I kept commands on my joplin book and I try to keep this gist updated. Maybe it can help you also.
Gist-Link  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://isaes.com.tr/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaes.com.tr/about/</guid>
      <description>Personal Details   İsa Eş
  Ümraniye/İstanbul
  merhaba@isaes.com.tr
  +90 (537)-976-ONE-SEVEN-84
   Experience Huawei Turkey R&amp;amp;D Center / Asst.Software Engineer / 2018/11-Current Understanding Telecom standard KPI measurements. Analyzing and understanding of Huawei Big Data solution for Telecommunication companies and developing enterprise applications for telecom companies.
Big Data analysis project developments for different telecom companies.
Roles:
Scala Developer at STC Projects (SAU)
 Given support to customer and developing assigned tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>